,tweets,user_name,location,geo,entities,sentiment
0,"Gawat! Kasus Infeksi Covid-19 Tembus 100.000, WFH Bakal Diberlakukan Lagi? ",motorplusweekly,"Jakarta, Indonesia",,"[('Kasus Infeksi', 'PERSON'), ('Tembus', 'GPE'), ('Bakal Diberlakukan Lagi', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
1, Emangnya karyawan test covid-19 ke CEO? Kok bisa CEO nutupin hasil karyawannya?Karyawannya cek Fas… ,TeamYuigahama,Jakarta Indonesia,,"[('Kok bisa', 'PERSON'), ('karyawannya?Karyawannya', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
2,My friend lost her father to COVID-19. Please donate to her family.  Thank you ✨,bane_cc,,,[],"{'neg': 0.113, 'neu': 0.493, 'pos': 0.394, 'compound': 0.6908}"
3,"CG PPHT 2020: Exam (Cancelled), Admit Card, Pattern, Syllabus CG PPHT 2020 Examination has… ",Eduportplus,,,"[('Admit Card', 'PERSON'), ('Pattern', 'NORP'), ('Syllabus CG PPHT', 'PRODUCT'), ('2020', 'CARDINAL'), ('Examination', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.878, 'pos': 0.122, 'compound': 0.2023}"
4,  Pablo Casado pide mando único para combatir el Covid porque llamarlo estado de alarma le h… ,AndrsGa08263745,,,"[('mando único para', 'ORG'), ('de alarma le h…', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
5," Hilarious article needs to be retitled, 'Covid virus making the Rich into Socialists' as they wait for more bailouts.",jasoncaro,Texas,,"[('Socialists', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.27, 'compound': 0.743}"
6,"""Tkt y'aura pas de 2ème vague du covid""La deuxième vague : ",MoahRikunelOff,Viroflay,,"[(""Tkt y'aura pas de 2ème"", 'WORK_OF_ART')]","{'neg': 0.259, 'neu': 0.741, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2023}"
7,"""If she caught covid during the 2nd chemo cycle her likelihoodof dying was increased..."" so they took the chemo awa… ",Mabel_Mouse_,,,"[('2nd', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
8,"According to Johns Hopkins, the USA ends 7/27 with 4,294,770 confirmed cases of Covid-19. That is 60,750 more cases… ",Infoseepage,"Bellevue, WA",,"[('Johns Hopkins', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('7/27', 'CARDINAL'), ('4,294,770', 'CARDINAL'), ('60,750', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
9,,bolon65348297,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
10,SPOTLIGHT: How rugby legend Broadhurst Cona beat Covid-19 ,SpotlightNSP,"Cape Town, South Africa",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
11, Don’t u knew you can only die from covid! This country has gone completely insane!,jan_cam001,,,[],"{'neg': 0.384, 'neu': 0.616, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8165}"
12,    The U.S. gov. commits to 300 million doses of a future v… ,Pastor_Gabe,"Junction City, KS",,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('300 million', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.901, 'pos': 0.099, 'compound': 0.0258}"
13,  Not sure about the vacancies metric. If you were a business that closed due covid and are re… ,KevGwy,"Galway, Ireland",,[],"{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2411}"
14,"Covid-19 salgını nedeniyle son 24 saatte Hindistan'da 654, Brezilya'da 614, Meksika'da 342 kişi hayatını kaybetti. ",yeni1mecra,iletisim@yeni1mecra.com,,"[('Covid-19 salgını', 'PERSON'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), (""Hindistan'da 654"", 'PRODUCT'), (""Brezilya'da 614"", 'PRODUCT'), (""Meksika'da 342"", 'FAC'), ('kişi hayatını kaybetti', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
15,#DIRECTO | El 🏥 Marañón lidera un estudio de síndrome inflamatorio en niños con Covid-19,redaccionmedica,España,,"[('| El 🏥 Marañón', 'PERSON'), ('un estudio de síndrome', 'PERSON'), ('niños con', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
16, Yes but Germany has a substantially lower rate of Covid than the UK.#r4today,MaisonGladys,Liguria ,,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.215, 'neu': 0.663, 'pos': 0.123, 'compound': -0.3377}"
17,"""You've got this"" is probably the most uplifting way to let someone know they've contracted covid.",blurstinshow,Toronto Ontario Canada,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
18,"Un medicament anti-COVID, testat la Spitalul Toma Ciorbă din Capitală ",pagesmoldova,Chisinau,,"[('Un', 'ORG'), ('Spitalul Toma Ciorbă', 'FAC')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
19, Exactly! Look at what’s happening right now with covid tenders. People are jumping into defence of looter… ,RSZungu87,"KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa ",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.82, 'pos': 0.18, 'compound': 0.3164}"
20,     Tumre kejariwal ne th congress k samane ha… ,mohanhatehypo,India,,"[('kejariwal', 'ORG'), ('congress', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
21,Guwahati: 60 new COVID-19 counselling centres start functioning ,NewsLiveGhy,"Guwahati, India",,"[('60', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
22,"   All of these insane clown posses, from Covid to riots to racist slande… ",TMterrific,Great American Southwest,,"[('Covid', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.5, 'neu': 0.5, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.875}"
23,  And I use ffp2 or ffp3 mask if dealing with Covid not a soggy piece of cloth. Those who… ,edwardm98619715,Munich ,,"[('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
24,My pet for COVID 19 lol ,idjlex,"New York, NY",,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.641, 'pos': 0.359, 'compound': 0.4215}"
25,  Why disinfect your whole house when COVID is primarily transmitted in an aerosol form and not on surf… ,alaskafatcat,"Alaska, USA",,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
26, Eso lo dijo un llanito (uno de Gibraltar) en un audio que me pasaron cuando empezó lo del covid 🤣,santibone,A Fire at a Sea Parks,,"[('Eso', 'PERSON'), ('uno de Gibraltar', 'ORG'), ('un', 'ORG'), ('lo del', 'PERSON'), ('🤣', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
27,Combato con 2 tipos de virus:1) El covid-192) La ignorancia de las personas a cerca del covid-19,Rudolf_rap_,El país de las maravillas,,"[('2 tipos', 'MONEY'), ('de las', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
28,"With regard to sharp rise in COVID-19 cases in Jammu&amp; KashmirAs per the orders, tertiary care hospitals in Sringar… ",GulistanNewsTV,Jammu And Kashmir,,"[('Sringar', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.849, 'pos': 0.151, 'compound': 0.4939}"
29,"  Is not really looking like this covid situation will be leaving soon,I think our gove… ",oladejograce,"Ikorodu, Nigeria",,[],"{'neg': 0.142, 'neu': 0.858, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3217}"
30,"ppl,, wala po akong covid ha hehe sinipon lang ako kasi tangina ng nagpaiyak sakin hehehe :-))))))))",ashdrd,National Capital Region,,"[('ppl', 'ORG'), ('wala po akong', 'PERSON'), ('lang ako kasi tangina', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.171, 'neu': 0.714, 'pos': 0.114, 'compound': -0.296}"
31,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,MadAmethyst,,,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
32,If R500 Billion could not create enough jobs what could that R70Bn will do?After COVID we going to owe everyone.,Mr_Mosoeu," Pretoria, South Africa (012)",,"[('Billion', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.087, 'neu': 0.913, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2057}"
33, What a terrible idea!Remind our feckless Chancellor to slash carparking prices then and build more road… ,Head4Heights,Europe,,"[('idea!Remind', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.297, 'neu': 0.703, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6696}"
34,"      Sir, it's a high request p… ",AparnaGarg19,"इंदिरा पुरम, गाज़ियाबाद",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
35, The censorship of covid data.  See frontline doctors.,SteveLechner,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
36, Yale Doctor!,WillGSmith1,San Diego,,"[('Yale', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
37,"Mask, Protective Suit, Gloves and other Covid protection items for wholesale.A manufacturer in China, looking forw… ",LiuJie15700423,,,"[('Protective Suit', 'ORG'), ('Gloves', 'ORG'), ('Covid', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
38, Kung wala lang covid e hahaahaha,babybuff_,home,,"[('Kung wala', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
39,"   compañera de una clínica en málaga, tenemos su permiso para la difus… ",paraisoperdido8,,,"[('tenemos su permiso para la difus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
40,"POLSEK CIKANDE POLRES SERANG, Pastikan Kamtibmas Tetap Kondusif, Aipda Suriat Bhabinkamtibmas Desa Nambo Ilir Kec.… ",CkdHumas,,,"[('Pastikan', 'NORP'), ('Kamtibmas Tetap Kondusif', 'PERSON'), ('Desa Nambo Ilir Kec', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
41,"As of 28 July 2020, 1:35 pm, there are 22 active COVID-19 cases at the Presidential Communications Operations Offic… ",PhilippineStar,Philippines,,"[('28 July 2020', 'DATE'), ('1:35 pm', 'TIME'), ('22', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Presidential Communications Operations Offic', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.4019}"
42,Full points on governance in UP to Yogi Adityanath....public feels mark improvement in every sector...good work ple… ,aamadme,,,"[('UP', 'GPE'), ('Yogi Adityanath', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.842, 'pos': 0.158, 'compound': 0.4588}"
43, My Uncle is COVID Positive and admitted to Shatabdi hospital kandiwali (W). Ward M bed no. 19. We want… ,Rajeev2Rana,,,"[('COVID Positive', 'ORG'), ('Shatabdi', 'LAW'), ('Ward M', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.099, 'neu': 0.676, 'pos': 0.225, 'compound': 0.4215}"
44,This is my year of servicing bad debt that I have accumulated over a period of 5 years... The past 5 years can only… ,The_ElecticZulu,"Bloemfontein, South Africa",,"[('5 years', 'DATE'), ('The past 5 years', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.25, 'neu': 0.75, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7184}"
45, nenek tu tau tak covid suka orang tua 😭,nrwanii_,,,"[('nenek tu tau tak', 'PERSON'), ('suka orang tua', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
46, Trump said it was potentially good and may help people with covid issues and they can never admit he was right,JacqGame,,,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.063, 'neu': 0.715, 'pos': 0.222, 'compound': 0.6134}"
47,"We do not know many Malaysians carry Covid-19 without symptoms. Now, the authorities allow people to go back to vil… ",Senggiaw,,,"[('Malaysians', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.909, 'pos': 0.091, 'compound': 0.2263}"
48, Hope she gets Covid,RapidEyeMoveme2,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.508, 'pos': 0.492, 'compound': 0.4404}"
49, Why the school is open during Covid-19?,xainab_Umair,"Islamabad, Pakistan",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
50,COVID has literally made me hate my job.,Milan__Monroe,"San Francisco, CA",,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.346, 'neu': 0.654, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5719}"
51," Still, those are still wrong, having a thousand people gathering in one place without proper covid protocol.",urwande,,,"[('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.171, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4767}"
52,Data Center Market Analysis Highlights the Impact of COVID-19 (2020-2024) | Rise in Adoption of Edge...… ,dicerod,"Miami, FL",,"[('Data Center Market Analysis', 'ORG'), ('2020-2024', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
53, I am sure they use Hydrochloroquine to prevent Covid.,EALStokes,,,"[('Hydrochloroquine', 'ORG'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.638, 'pos': 0.362, 'compound': 0.34}"
54, Pero se ha hecho la prueba del COVID o no?,jbadenes,,,"[('Pero', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.19, 'neu': 0.603, 'pos': 0.207, 'compound': 0.0516}"
55,The COVID-19 pandemic and access to public water in Lagos  #vanguardnews ,vanguardngrnews,Nigeria,,"[('Lagos', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
56,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,Vickimcc101,"North West, England",,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
57,Makabugo maning covid oy yawa,biamcst,Republic of the Philippines ,,"[('Makabugo', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
58,‘I didn’t know my brother was dying of COVID in a Florida prison — until the hospital called’ |...… ,izafoodie,"Miami, FL via Trinidad",,"[('COVID', 'ORG'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.171, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5106}"
59,  Pablo Casado pide mando único para combatir el Covid porque llamarlo estado de alarm… ,AndrsGa08263745,,,"[('mando único para', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
60,Sawahlunto sebelumnya zona hijau Covid-19. ,kompascom,Indonesia,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
61,  In Florida &amp; 1 in Georgia. Both States where COVID’s an raging out of control Fire t… ,Tiggersk8,Northeastern Ontario,,"[('Florida &amp', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.293, 'neu': 0.707, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7003}"
62,Hinds: Still no clear answer where latest COVID-19 cases came from - Loop News Trinidad and Tobago...… ,TriniTweets,"Port of Spain, T&T",,"[('Trinidad', 'GPE'), ('Tobago', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.117, 'neu': 0.745, 'pos': 0.138, 'compound': 0.1027}"
63,"FQ:  Strage di Bologna, quest’anno niente corteo per le regole anti Covid. Merola: “Scelta dolorosa, ma abbiamo il… ",MPenikas,,,"[('Scelta', 'NORP'), ('ma abbiamo il', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.119, 'neu': 0.881, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3182}"
64,Hinds: Still no clear answer where latest COVID-19 cases came from - Loop News Trinidad and Tobago...… ,izatrini,"Miami, FL",,"[('Trinidad', 'GPE'), ('Tobago', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.117, 'neu': 0.745, 'pos': 0.138, 'compound': 0.1027}"
65,"Après le Covid-19, retour à la normale pour les #DRH ? via   ",Olga_ACOUETEY,92 NANTERRE,,"[('Après le Covid-19', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
66,Covid-19 has accelerated digitalization and #datacenter growth. They all need #cooling to ensure a secure data flow… ,efficient_EE,Feldkirchen,,"[('Covid-19', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.631, 'pos': 0.369, 'compound': 0.765}"
67,#Covid #Dashboard #ChennaiOnly #13K_peoples are under treatment 🔥🌱✌️ ,Gangatharanvks,"Chennai, India",,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
68,We need more of this...These BRAVE front-line doctors are EXPOSING the truth about the COVID Hoax RIGHT NOW!Docto… ,ColleenKRich,Citizen of Earth,,"[('the COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.19, 'neu': 0.54, 'pos': 0.27, 'compound': 0.4688}"
69,    I heard he took advantage of COVID and had a 65% increase,Markisslump,between sherri shepherd's tits,,"[('COVID', 'ORG'), ('65%', 'PERCENT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.65, 'pos': 0.35, 'compound': 0.5106}"
70,"Hydroxychloroquine is not an effective treatment for COVID-19, according to the FDA  ",DawnMarie817,Los Angeles,,"[('FDA', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.188, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3724}"
71,MLB covid cases: Will Cincinnati Reds see an outbreak? | Opinion ,stuartcohen821,"Louisville, Kentucky",,"[('Will Cincinnati Reds', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
72,"MEITY wanted protocol for all governing all COVID-19 data, not just Aarogya Setu: RTI  ",ETTRSS,"Indiana, USA",,"[('Aarogya Setu: RTI', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
73,"¿CÓMO SI NADA? 🚫 Así es como Petare reacciona ante la ""cuarentena radical"" (➕info) 👇🏼  ⬇ ",CaraotaDigital,Caracas - Venezuela,,"[('¿', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
74, As I understand it the RNA PCR test cannot distinguish between active live virus and RNA remnants sti… ,martindale567,,,"[('RNA', 'ORG'), ('RNA', 'ORG'), ('sti', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.876, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3089}"
75,"Il cantante toscano replica sulle parole pronunciate al convegno: ""Non sono un negazionista, sono un ottimista e ri… ",iltirreno,Livorno,,"[('Il', 'GPE'), ('replica sulle', 'PERSON'), ('pronunciate al convegno', 'PERSON'), ('un', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
76,"As we as community struggle with the tragedies of the Covid crisis, we can learn from  disaster recovery agency… ",Dyslexicpastor,"West yorkshire, england",,"[('Covid', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.472, 'neu': 0.528, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9246}"
77,"Child malnutrition and COVID-19: the time to act is now  by H Fore, dr Tedros et al.",KristofDecoste1,,,"[('H Fore', 'PERSON'), ('Tedros et al', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
78,Best la pulak bila paham internasional trade. covid 19 effects apa semo. Padu sia,VenicciLaa,"Upper Greenwood Lake, NJ",,"[('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.756, 'pos': 0.244, 'compound': 0.6369}"
79,"Following ATP500 in Tokyo, WTA Toray Pan Pacific Open tennis tournament in Tokyo (scheduled in November) has been c… ",Vestige_du_jour,,,"[('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('November', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
80,Siapa yang mau jadi relawan uji klinis vaksin covid-19? Tim riset uji klinis vaksin Covid-19 Unpad mulai membuka pe… ,Genpi_Co,Indonesia,,"[('Siapa yang mau jadi', 'PERSON'), ('Tim', 'PERSON'), ('Unpad mulai membuka', 'QUANTITY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
81,       … ,DamianOlko,Warszawa,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
82,"COVID and its response is eugenics. The ""OK Boomer Virus"", comprenden? #Bioterrorism #CCPVirus ",AlexisH13876559,,,"[('COVID', 'ORG'), ('The ""OK Boomer Virus""', 'PRODUCT'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.804, 'pos': 0.196, 'compound': 0.4466}"
83, Nope. My 64 year old mom has busted her ass this entire time going to work at a daycare and has finall… ,BrooklynnC81,"Carmel, IN",,"[('Nope', 'ORG'), ('64 year old', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.149, 'neu': 0.851, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5423}"
84,"I saw an ad on Twitter for ""special vision"" glasses that enable the wearer to see Covid in the air. ",badwebsites,,,"[('Twitter', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.783, 'pos': 0.217, 'compound': 0.5719}"
85,"Frontline worker, Fought with Covid-19 within me, Donated blood to save life. Battle of the Year. It's a Victory… ",KipenLongkumer,"Kohima, Nagaland",,"[('Frontline', 'ORG'), ('the Year', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.212, 'neu': 0.649, 'pos': 0.139, 'compound': -0.1779}"
86,  One more difference is there due to covid...July ending ka pressure nhi h bhaiii..😂,Surbhisukheja1,Gwalior,,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('July', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.155, 'neu': 0.845, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
87,  FRAUDCI is being COVID censored!,RoseMalloy5,Ireland and USA,,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.321, 'neu': 0.679, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2244}"
88,Ojito con los de  que te venden un seguro con unas condiciones que luego no sean reales! ( habló de cancelac… ,lovg21,,,"[('Ojito con los', 'PERSON'), ('un', 'ORG'), ('habló de cancelac', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.116, 'neu': 0.884, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3595}"
89," inviting leaders and teachers to take action, re-imagine education and use Covid-19 as a catalyst for t… ",Feresh99,"South Australia, Australia",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.867, 'pos': 0.133, 'compound': 0.3182}"
90,To com uma leve tosse vamos de COVID,iJuau,"Niterói, Brasil",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
91,And the old man they knocked to the ground. Also Covid? What Covid? ,speechwithease,"San Diego, CA",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
92,"COVID-19 No Vaccine Needed, There Is Already A Cure - NewsBlaze News#covid #CovidVaccineRace… ",NiravVansia,India,,"[('CovidVaccineRace', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.18, 'neu': 0.82, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
93,"Face-to-face classes, papayagan sa Enero kapag may bakuna laban sa COVID-19",DZAR1026,"ACQ Tower, Makati City, Phil.",,"[('papayagan sa', 'PERSON'), ('Enero kapag', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
94,"Heaven gaining all angels up there mahn, fuck this covid thing, my childhood friend buried by strange people, no fa… ",Danstro_,25 resident,,[],"{'neg': 0.244, 'neu': 0.455, 'pos': 0.302, 'compound': 0.4215}"
95,    maksutnya kan dia udh setuju dan berani juga buat sakit covi… ,ahmaless,dimana aja yg penting nyaman,,"[('dan berani juga', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
96,"Negazionisti del Covid, la replica di Bocelli alle polemiche: 'Accadono cose strane, sono stato fra…  via ",BirbaeEmilia,"Illinois, USA",,"[('Negazionisti del Covid', 'PERSON'), ('la replica', 'FAC'), ('Bocelli', 'FAC')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
97,"The Marlins' COVID-19 outbreak is really bad, and exactly what MLB signed up for  via ",sacollectibles,"san antonio, tx",,"[('Marlins', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.213, 'neu': 0.787, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5849}"
98,"Trump Pushes Fake COVID Cure From Fringe Doctors, Banned by Facebook  via ",ps9714,"Fort Hood, TX",,[],"{'neg': 0.379, 'neu': 0.621, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7269}"
99,"MINHA PRIMA TA COM COVID E EU TAVA COM ELA ESSES DIA, CARA EU TO CHORANDO",__diasssz,🇧🇷,,"[('MINHA PRIMA TA', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
100,  This homophobic person that denies Covid is real has music on your site. I’m assuming yo… ,MintyMoses2019,,,"[('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.157, 'neu': 0.843, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4215}"
101,India has prepared five sites for the final human trials phase of the potential COVID-19 vaccine developed by Oxfor… ,NewsBytesApp,"Gurgaon, Haryana",,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Oxfor', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.905, 'pos': 0.095, 'compound': 0.2263}"
102, ,BridgetAshmore,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
103,Oh border y ulang alik tu tak bole bukak. Tkot covid. Y p berhimpun ramai2 tu covid tak datang singgah ke siot. Pen… ,aeenzmohdghzli,JOHOR BAHRU,,"[('y ulang', 'PERSON'), ('alik tu tak bole', 'PERSON'), ('ke siot', 'PERSON'), ('Pen', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
104,My neighbors had rented furniture from there. When I tell you they pulled up ringing my bell like I rented from the… ,TheeArtofJoJo,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.884, 'pos': 0.116, 'compound': 0.3612}"
105,"Jeden Einreisenden testen. Gepoolte Tests könnten die Kosten dafür senken. In Landkreisen mit größeren Ausbrüchen,… ",sero_01,Hessen Deutschland ,,"[('Jeden Einreisenden', 'PERSON'), ('Gepoolte Tests', 'PERSON'), ('Landkreisen', 'PERSON'), ('Ausbrüchen', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.218, 'neu': 0.782, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}"
106,"Anyone else lose friends due to Covid? Them not caring that the worlds in a pandemic, and your anxiety saying you n… ",cccaaaiiittt,"New Jersey, USA",,[],"{'neg': 0.259, 'neu': 0.627, 'pos': 0.114, 'compound': -0.4456}"
107,  Y que tal el pendejo del #CacasObrador de #Amlo que NO quiere que le pregunten por los muertos d… ,javier_etac,"Ciudad de México, DF",,"[('los muertos', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.147, 'neu': 0.853, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4466}"
108,"Et si la petite contre-partie de la liberté de se rassembler, c’était le respect des gestes barrières et l’app Stop… ",icambreleng,France,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.4767}"
109,"The Mamelodi Regional Hospital has been renovated in response to the #Covid_19 pandemic, chief executive Dr Naing S… ",IOL,South Africa,,"[('The Mamelodi Regional Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Naing S', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
110, I refuse to be chained by fake science. I have successfully treated over 250 COVID patients with HC… ,Chiquinho_JJ,,,"[('over 250', 'CARDINAL'), ('COVID', 'ORG'), ('HC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.247, 'neu': 0.605, 'pos': 0.149, 'compound': -0.2732}"
111,This hypocrisy and double standards is the reason people don’t comply #Lesotho government directives on COVID-19. T… ,MoMonyake,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
112,"  Obviously Nadler is on it or else is a bigger pos than I imagined, exposing his wife to covid… ",MediumGrace,"Los Angeles, CA",,"[('Nadler', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.116, 'neu': 0.884, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2732}"
113,        … ,AbhayMa10070532,India,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
114,"  Hahaha yes,  Trump personally went up and to all those people indavidually and have them Covid.",MblingBrdFrk,"Sacramento, CA",,"[('Hahaha', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.69, 'pos': 0.31, 'compound': 0.743}"
115, My booking id is NN2019045979654 I have booked return flight ticket from your company and flight got c… ,deepaky23792016,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
116, Kinda digging Dr. Druid in the current COVID-delayed run of Dr. Strange. ,HaroldJ_NEPA,,,"[('Kinda', 'PERSON'), ('Druid', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.141, 'neu': 0.859, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2023}"
117,"Les sanctions américaines contre l’Iran ont considérablement diminué les revenus du pays, compliquant aussi toute t… ",Allio_De_Corato,"Paris, France",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
118,COVID-19 UPDATE: Bilang ng mga gumaling sa virus sa Las Piñas lagpas 500 na! sa kasalukuyan nasa 503 na ang kabuuan… ,DonBuenvenida,💕 Nissin Riño Aceres 💕0530,,"[('Bilang', 'GPE'), ('500', 'CARDINAL'), ('na', 'ORG'), ('sa kasalukuyan', 'PERSON'), ('nasa', 'ORG'), ('503', 'CARDINAL'), ('na ang kabuuan', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
119,"The next time you complain about the rising prices of food, whether at fast food or at the grocery store, know ther… ",GalaxySquires,"Missoulalaland, MT",,[],"{'neg': 0.106, 'neu': 0.894, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3612}"
120,3 events of last summer and Covid 19 have probably shaped the current Chelsea situation with an intertwined relatio… ,CfcPbs,"Mumbai,India",,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('last summer', 'DATE'), ('Covid 19', 'FAC'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
121,"🙄🤨🤔🌞😷🌄👋🏞😉😝🤘🎧When The Time Comes, we'll be able to put all this COVID-19 Stuff behind Us;  ",BowyerDamian,Brisbane Qld Australia,,"[('🙄\U0001f928', 'PERSON'), ('Us', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
122,"Kinda over this no working thing , fck COVID 🙄",SkizzyB_,,,"[('Kinda', 'ORG'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.237, 'neu': 0.763, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2893}"
123,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,ClaireMedler,"England, United Kingdom",,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
124,•NCC Begins Implementation of Revised Telecoms Service Level Agreements*Private Institutions To Benefit From TETFu… ,olapeckham,"Ikeja, Nigeria",,"[('Implementation of Revised Telecoms Service Level Agreements*Private Institutions To Benefit', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.188, 'compound': 0.4588}"
125,Conduct last rites of COVID-19 suspects without waiting for test report: Odisha govt to Collectors ,republic,"Mumbai, India",,"[('Odisha', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.146, 'neu': 0.854, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.34}"
126,"(L'express): #Crise du #Covid-19 : la bataille économique se joue maintenant : Dans un peu moins d'un mois, le gouv… ",titrespresse,,,"[('Crise', 'PERSON'), ('la bataille', 'PERSON'), ('Dans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
127,negazionisti del covid e negazionisti di calciopoli 1 e 2.Non so chi mi fa piu' pena.E diciamo che in entrambi i… ,dydsix,"Budapest, Hungary",,"[('negazionisti del covid', 'PERSON'), ('calciopoli 1 e', 'FAC'), (""chi mi fa piu'"", 'PERSON'), ('diciamo che', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
128,"Venga, vamos a morirnos de hambre todos. Cuando dejéis de recibir dinerito en vuestros bolsillos cada mes, veréis… ",As_de_Pecas,,,"[('Venga', 'PERSON'), ('cada mes', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
129,"Really scared about tomorrow, if we wake up and half the Phillies have covid we are screwed...😥 I hope this doesn't age well",HippoPlays25,"St Louis, MO",,"[('tomorrow', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.186, 'neu': 0.706, 'pos': 0.108, 'compound': -0.2748}"
130, Also please see this document imposing COVID tax on the import of the same. ,Aapka_Neighbour,"Madridejos, España",,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.089, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.146, 'compound': 0.2263}"
131," Take money out of politics, political leadership will be left for selfless people. Take the billions o… ",danielaremufory,Lagos/Abuja,,"[('billions', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
132,(Mediapart): #Recherche contre le Covid-19: la place de Bill Gates et des #VIP interroge : Bill Gates est devenu un… ,titrespresse,,,"[('Mediapart', 'ORG'), ('Recherche', 'PERSON'), ('de Bill Gates', 'PERSON'), ('Bill Gates', 'PERSON'), ('un', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
133, The Dem covid bill send $25 million to the Kennedy Center for the Arts so they wouldn't furlough any… ,Ddgr_Fan_1976,"Texas, USA",,"[('$25 million', 'MONEY'), ('the Kennedy Center for the Arts', 'FAC')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
134,F**k  covid-19!40th Crusell Music Festival 2021 gonna be a blast! Welcome Olli! #crusellmusicfestival… ,Tuomas_Takala,,,"[('Crusell Music Festival 2021', 'ORG'), ('Olli', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.586, 'pos': 0.414, 'compound': 0.795}"
135,   And after 8 weeks if it hasn't worked? Or a month later we get another wave?,HoldsworthCJ,"Melbourne, Australia",,"[('8 weeks', 'DATE'), ('a month later', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
136, Este gobierno no está gestionando bien el tema covid.....,MaraGarcaJuare2,Sant Just desvern,,"[('gestionando bien el tema covid', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.216, 'neu': 0.784, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
137,    No cure yet my uncle who lives in a 3rd world country BT… ,SamLatino4Trump,,,"[('3rd', 'ORDINAL'), ('BT', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.167, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
138, Whats unbelievable is that you`re complaining that people are reducing the chance (no matter how s… ,prings64,Middle Earth,,[],"{'neg': 0.096, 'neu': 0.642, 'pos': 0.262, 'compound': 0.2732}"
139,Covid 19 da Filiasyona sanki ilk baştaki gibi önem verilmiyor!!Temasli kişiye evinde PCR testi alınmalı ve 14 gün… ,profvefikarica,"İstanbul, Türkiye",,"[('da Filiasyona', 'PERSON'), ('kişiye', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
140,Sometimes I remember how Covid-19 ruined everything from me and I start feeling really depressed. But then I realiz… ,nataliamolinaba,,,[],"{'neg': 0.316, 'neu': 0.613, 'pos': 0.071, 'compound': -0.7346}"
141,"Funny how some things can be news. Which really are not they are just him doing his job. But other things, like the… ",juliasilvertop,"Melbourne, Victoria",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.795, 'pos': 0.205, 'compound': 0.6597}"
142,     They are taking care of these patients. Are you serious… ,swesterfield1,"Trenton, Ohio",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.738, 'pos': 0.262, 'compound': 0.4939}"
143, I’m just going to this here: ,aeolianD,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
144,Trump and Elon were right. HCQ was the cure for Covid. We’ve all been lied and played for politic gain. Arrests nee… ,luismen1991,"New York, NY",,"[('Trump', 'PRODUCT'), ('Elon', 'PRODUCT'), ('HCQ', 'ORG'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.188, 'neu': 0.614, 'pos': 0.198, 'compound': 0.0772}"
145,Yo ni en tiempos de Covid la dejo de cagar ☹️,KimberlyReyesC4,Moravia / Puntarenas,,"[('Yo ni en tiempos de Covid la dejo de cagar ☹️', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
146,Latin America leads world in COVID-19 cases  ,anadoluagency,Ankara - TURKEY,,"[('Latin America', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
147,   If there is any time in American life when the federal government is su… ,LoveKeithO,,,"[('American', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
148,My new post-Covid hobby will be pretending like I'm recording Cameo greetings on my phone while in public.,kennycity,,,"[('Cameo', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.691, 'pos': 0.309, 'compound': 0.6908}"
149,$NVAXTexas biotech facility in College Station tapped to mass-produce potential COVID-19 vaccine… ,TOWiU2,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
150,  India’s COVID Mortality rate is the lowest in the world. And that is the statistic which matte… ,7notesndreams,,,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('COVID Mortality', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.14, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}"
151,"On Mon, July 27th, 596 deaths were reported from Covid in the US per Worldometer. This is 72 higher from last Mon… ",AnonBecauseOf,,,"[('July 27th', 'DATE'), ('596', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Worldometer', 'GPE'), ('72', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
152,"So, in my monthly one on one meeting with my manager just before my vacation (directly before COVID took over the c… ",tinksflight,,,"[('monthly', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
153,  I and my kids are up to date on all our vaccinations and get flu shots every year. I'… ,aaronpelly,"Tri-Cities, Washington",,"[('every year', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.133, 'neu': 0.867, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}"
154,Talk about overkill by the government! I get why there’s a 14 day quarantine for people coming back from their holi… ,Wobblegob1,That Middlesbrough,,"[('14 day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
155,"Diario de una dependienta en tiempos de Covid.. -Buenos días, tiene que ponerse la mascarilla-Ay!! es que me agob… ",mppozuelo,Spain,,"[('Diario de una', 'ORG'), ('tiempos de Covid', 'PERSON'), ('tiene que ponerse', 'PERSON'), ('es que', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
156, Pablo Casado pide mando único para combatir el Covid porque llamarlo estado de alarma le haría parecer imbécil...más imbécil.,AndrsGa08263745,,,"[('Pablo Casado', 'PERSON'), ('mando único para', 'ORG'), ('de alarma', 'PERSON'), ('más imbécil', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
157,1st attack dog is out to lay ground work narrative Johnson Hancock et al didn't needlessly kill 1000s 500l care sta… ,Annie17Lois,European Union,,"[('1st', 'DATE'), ('Johnson Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('1000s', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.111, 'neu': 0.642, 'pos': 0.247, 'compound': 0.5911}"
158,Please watch before they take it down,ghlinksnews,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.723, 'pos': 0.277, 'compound': 0.3182}"
159,  I wonder how scarcity has increased during COVID and what impact that has had?,ruth_dale,"South West, England",,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.851, 'pos': 0.149, 'compound': 0.2732}"
160,PCOO Asec. JV Arcena says COVID-19 cases at PCOO main office is now at 22 active cases. Another active case was rec… ,JMAurelioINQ,"Manila, PHL",,"[('PCOO Asec', 'ORG'), ('PCOO', 'ORG'), ('22', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.787, 'pos': 0.213, 'compound': 0.6597}"
161,Bogus - even if Heavens provide Bank Guarantee who will pay Nitu 40-50 Crore if Nitu refuses to give 80% shares to… ,QEBNA,"Kolkata, India",,"[('Heavens provide Bank Guarantee', 'ORG'), ('40-50', 'CARDINAL'), ('80%', 'PERCENT')]","{'neg': 0.055, 'neu': 0.672, 'pos': 0.273, 'compound': 0.6705}"
162,I’m now experiencing why the saying “life comes at you fast” is still a thing. Fuck COVID 🖕,manaclips,,,"[('Fuck COVID', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.189, 'neu': 0.811, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5423}"
163,#CuarentenaEnLaCityDoctor...cuando una persona sale positiva por covid 19 hizo aislamiento y la EPS dio de alta al… ,RosanaAvila9,B,,"[('cuando una', 'PERSON'), ('por', 'ORG'), ('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
164,   Kesinlikle aptallik Adamin babasi covid+ ise cocuguna eşine nasil test… ,BOZMOZY,,,"[('Kesinlikle', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
165,VIDEO: Covid-19 and “The Spiderweb of Fear”. American Medical Doctors and Health Experts are being Silenced…… ,IzabelleAslani1,,,"[('“The Spiderweb of Fear”', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('American Medical Doctors and Health Experts', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
166,Im at that Breakfast buffet i twote about over the weekend and aksafani because covid😫,Wentzello,"Johannesburg | Florida, NY",,"[('Breakfast', 'GPE'), ('the weekend', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
167,  They have already done that one maonth back thats why the person got his money back. Don't… ,SahaBodhisatwa,বাংলা,,"[('one maonth', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
168,hydroxyqlouroquine cures covid FACT!,ernesto_eu_out,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
169, cancer patients were just dumped by the government.  My husbands op was cancelled 3 times during the Covid pan… ,Amandah84044681,,,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.378, 'neu': 0.622, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8442}"
170,"Demande de patients ""leur employeur respectif à lui et son épouse, Solène Herry, leur réclame un certificat médical… ",Docmemepaspeur,,,"[('Solène Herry', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
171,J’dois aller faire le test du covid là g l’démon,piste01_,Lille,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
172,Kemarin jumlah kasus positif sudah menembus angka psikologis 100 ribu. Tepatnya 100.303.  ,kaltim_post,Balikpapan,,"[('Kemarin jumlah kasus', 'PERSON'), ('menembus', 'ORG'), ('100', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
173,சுப்ரீம் குழுமத்தின் நிர்வாக இயக்குனர் திரு.AMA.SIDDIQ அவர்களுக்கு 2020 ஆம் ஆண்டு சிறந்த சமூக சேவகர் (REAL HEROS OF… ,supremegroups,kuwait,,"[('2020', 'CARDINAL'), ('ஆம்', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.178, 'compound': 0.4648}"
174, See the connection with their deaths and covid 19 ? The Prime Minister Trudeau and Hilliary Clinton are… ,ChownLloyd,,,"[('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trudeau', 'PERSON'), ('Hilliary Clinton', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
175,"Covid-19 tally crosses 7,000 mark, two more deaths reported in Indore | Indore News ",indoregranth,"Indore, India",,"[('7,000 mark', 'MONEY'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indore | Indore\xa0News', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
176,#CoronaVirusUpdate 🇵🇰Pakistan’s #COVID_19 regional comparison#APPNews #Pakistan #COVID19 #EidUlAdha_Covid19… ,appcsocialmedia,"Islamabad, Pakistan",,"[('🇵', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), '', ('comparison#APPNews #Pakistan #COVID19', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
177,"Think theologically: Your church's relaunch (Lionel Windsor, Mikey Lynch, Andrew Heard). As Covid-19 restrictions b… ",lionelwindsor,"Newtown, Sydney, Australia",,"[('Lionel Windsor', 'PERSON'), ('Mikey Lynch', 'GPE'), ('Andrew Heard', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
178,  and a negative covid test needed from one of UAE approved centres &amp; travel insurance sta… ,claral72,Down South,,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('UAE', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.19, 'neu': 0.667, 'pos': 0.144, 'compound': -0.2263}"
179, He must confess what he did . We can see now that government hides behind covid 19 and threatening h… ,donald_mufamadi,"Soweto, South Africa",,"[('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.231, 'neu': 0.769, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6249}"
180,"El pelotón de la Vuelta a Burgos tiene un hueco, en concreto el dorsal 116 del Israel Start-Up Nation. El equipo de… ",NievesMoya,,,"[('El pelotón de la Vuelta', 'ORG'), ('Burgos', 'GPE'), ('El', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
181,#CoronaVirusUpdate 🇵🇰Pakistan’s #COVID_19 regional comparison#APPNews #Pakistan #COVID19 #EidUlAdha_Covid19… ,appcsocialmedia,"Islamabad, Pakistan",,"[('🇵', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), '', ('comparison#APPNews #Pakistan #COVID19', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
182," Didn’t ya hear, they’re all taking HCQ, they aren’t afraid of Covid!",shellyt561,"Texas, USA",,"[('HCQ', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
183,‘That’s Ridiculous.’ How America’s Coronavirus Response Looks Abroad. ,SebastianStinky,,,"[('America', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
184,"Covid-19, this is your last chance to impress me and save yourself from elimination. ",YennAbdullah,"Selangor, Malaysia",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.576, 'pos': 0.424, 'compound': 0.7964}"
185,   Senza una postilla “[…] IN ASSENZA DI ADEGUATI DPI” in pratica state dicen… ,albiz94,Verona,,"[('pratica', 'GPE'), ('dicen', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
186, TOLONG QUARANTINE KAN SEMUA YANG PERGI NI . KALAU TAKNAK COVID MELANDA SMULAAAAA !!!!!!,byyraraaaaa,,,"[('TOLONG', 'ORG'), ('YANG PERGI NI', 'ORG'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
187," Also,a Yale doctor.",WillGSmith1,San Diego,,"[('Yale', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
188,Meant to be getting on a plane and heading to New York this week... thank you COVID-19 for ruining a trip 10 years… ,brownand_gold,"Sunshine Coast, Queensland",,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('10 years', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.809, 'pos': 0.106, 'compound': 0.128}"
189,"Anei aku whakaaro mo te hunga kua hoki mai ki te utu mo ta ratou ake wehenga. Yes those returning for weddings, fun… ",teaokatoa,Kirikiriroa / Hamilton ,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.109, 'compound': 0.4019}"
190,"Me for months of COVID life: Probably I have insomnia because I'm watching tv at night. If I would just read, I'd g… ",lindstorian,"Illinois, USA",,"[('months', 'DATE'), ('COVID', 'ORG'), ('night', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
191,"भारत में COVID-19 के कुल मामले 14.83 लाख हुए, पिछले 24 घंटे में 47,703 नए केस, 654 की मौत ",TahkikatSmachar,"Uttar Pradesh, India",,"[('14.83', 'CARDINAL'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('47,703 नए केस', 'QUANTITY'), ('654', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
192,  CDC &amp; WHO have definitely been behind. I'm interested in hearing your theories/evidence on fec… ,PamBaker3,"USA, Love it or GTFOH",,"[('CDC &amp', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.707, 'pos': 0.293, 'compound': 0.6597}"
193,   Except that it's simply not true that they're just mild:… ,hildabast,,,[],"{'neg': 0.206, 'neu': 0.794, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3252}"
194, 2005 NIH said chloroquine kills SARS-COVID.,RichardCkark,"Athens, AL",,"[('2005', 'DATE'), ('NIH', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.412, 'neu': 0.588, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5423}"
195,Agree with AndrewPlus 1: establishments can just as easily insist on Covid app checkin as they can on possessing… ,lancewiggs,Auckland,,"[('AndrewPlus 1', 'ORG'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.776, 'pos': 0.224, 'compound': 0.5994}"
196, This started with an attack of the elderly and the pro maskers need reminding of this. Instead of pointi… ,EdersonsArmy,United Kingdom,,[],"{'neg': 0.147, 'neu': 0.853, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4767}"
197,"Bagmana tingkat akurasi tes swab sih? Ini si Wawali dinyatakan positif covid setelah swab bbrp hr lalu. Nah, sekara… ",efrindu,"Surakarta, Jawa Tengah",,"[('Bagmana tingkat akurasi', 'ORG'), ('tes swab sih', 'PERSON'), ('Ini', 'PERSON'), ('Wawali', 'PERSON'), ('hr lalu', 'PERSON'), ('Nah', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.072, 'neu': 0.928, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}"
198,This is a prime example of everything that is wrong when things are done in a rush with little oversight. Apparentl… ,m_saakyan,"Los Angeles, California, USA",,"[('Apparentl', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.147, 'neu': 0.853, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4767}"
199,Read the thread on control data from Num 10 on Covid-19 Cummings mates who sat in on SAGE Data mining firm UK and… ,mmaher70,brighton,,"[('Num 10', 'EVENT'), ('Cummings', 'ORG'), ('SAGE Data', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
200,Daniel Andrews says he has no confidence in Victoria's private aged care Covid-19 response ,spiritgateoz,Australia,,"[('Daniel Andrews', 'PERSON'), ('Victoria', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.112, 'neu': 0.558, 'pos': 0.33, 'compound': 0.6486}"
201,i swear the COVID test gets worse and worse everytime 🥴,megan_lawrencex,"England, United Kingdom",,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.552, 'neu': 0.448, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7506}"
202, why are you advertising that a pet cat has been tested positive for COVID-19?  There is too much animal cr… ,sheilabrownowl,Worcestershire,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': 0.5574}"
203,Behavioral Health Software Market: High Demand for Mental Health in COVID-19 Pandemic by Prasad Shelke… ,health_care_new,India,,[],"{'neg': 0.097, 'neu': 0.903, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.128}"
204,,soskolsky,"Cullercoats,Newcastle, England",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
205,Can Restaurants Survive Shutting Down Again? ,MHSConsultancy,#LovinLeeds,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
206, लखनऊ विश्वविद्यालय द्वारा आयोजित होने वाली बीएड परीक्षा का सेंटर 200-300km दूर बनाया जा रहा है।।।ऐसे… ,PankajV88697334,"Allahabad, India",,"[('सेंटर 200-300km', 'MONEY'), ('बनाया', 'LAW')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
207,Our leadership might have missed a trick here: Russians report the number of people who recovered from Covid in one… ,NickJonsson1,Glasgow,,"[('Russians', 'NORP'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.164, 'neu': 0.773, 'pos': 0.063, 'compound': -0.2732}"
208,"Amerikaanse artsen tijdens persconferentie: “we have a cure to COVID-19, it’s hydroxychloroquine, azithromycin and… ",Saloemie,"Amsterdam, Nederland",,"[('artsen tijdens', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
209,American Doctors Address COVID-19 Misinformation with SCOTUS Press Conference  #BitChute,SamuellClair,,,"[('American Doctors Address COVID-19 Misinformation', 'ORG'), ('SCOTUS Press Conference', 'ORG'), ('BitChute', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.204, 'neu': 0.796, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3182}"
210,Frontline Physicians Aim to Dispel ‘Massive’ COVID-19 ‘Disinformation Ca...  via ,TrishaLFadeff,"Arizona, USA",,"[('Frontline', 'ORG'), ('Disinformation Ca', 'WORK_OF_ART')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
211,,FinchleyCentra1,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
212,Imagine hiring a group of young medical doctors to work at a call center to address Covid concerns then you still d… ,GasKip_,Bougie,,"[('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
213,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,Stacey15x,,,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
214,Please signThe Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disr… ,Glo_Thienel,,,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.276, 'neu': 0.628, 'pos': 0.096, 'compound': -0.6486}"
215,Pemerintah telah menetapkan program Pemulihan Ekonomi Nasional (PEN) dengan berbagai kebijakan menyasar masyarakat… ,setkabgoid,Jakarta,,"[('Pemerintah', 'ORG'), ('Pemulihan Ekonomi Nasional', 'ORG'), ('PEN', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
216," Acaban de subir los datos sobre el covid; solo el municipio tuvo 29 casos, creo que debería de impleme… ",playeron503,"Santa Tecla, El Salvador",,"[('Acaban', 'NORP'), ('29', 'CARDINAL'), ('casos', 'ORG'), ('que debería de impleme', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
217, PS: Congratulations! Sounds like you had a lovely intimate wedding day. I hope you get to celebrate w… ,Abbott_Psych,UCL Institute of Education ,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.392, 'pos': 0.608, 'compound': 0.9523}"
218,"If Our Dear Leader truly cared about unemployment and inequality, he wouldn't support the… ",fux0r,Durban,,[],"{'neg': 0.23, 'neu': 0.401, 'pos': 0.37, 'compound': 0.484}"
219,TV drama goes viral: the German-Danish series that foresaw Covid-19 ,makisstasinos,"Athens, Greece.",,"[('German', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
220,"Emirates will pay for your medical treatment, hotel quarantine, and even your funeral if you catch COVID-19 while t… ",Asmali77,"#Eastleigh, Nairobi ",,[],"{'neg': 0.187, 'neu': 0.813, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4404}"
221,"Hydroxychloroquine is not an effective treatment for COVID-19, according to the FDA  ",The1HeLetGetAwy,,,"[('FDA', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.188, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3724}"
222,"Dua pekan terakhir, kasus Covid-19 di Pekanbaru melonjak terutama dari klaster RS ",republikaonline,"Jakarta, Indonesia",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
223,People are dying and lives cut short from #cancer due to disruption in essential life saving treatment. Please sign ,coralroseradio,England UK ,,[],"{'neg': 0.201, 'neu': 0.699, 'pos': 0.1, 'compound': -0.3182}"
224,Después que pase el covid y mi futura e inexistente graduación me quiero ir a México como por dos meses o más.😓,louu_boo,El Salvador,,"[('México', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
225,Riposte COVID-19 : les Etats-Unis offrent du matériel informatique au gouvernement de Côte d’Ivoire ,ivoiremessages,COTE,,"[('les Etats-Unis', 'ORG'), ('du matériel informatique au', 'PERSON'), ('de Côte', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
226,so we either dying from covid or now from hand sanitizer.. i cannottTtT ,KayleighPerezz,19 ♐︎,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.775, 'pos': 0.225, 'compound': 0.4939}"
227, Humble request form you sir /mam please save our life🙌 some of the family have one child we are not b… ,AbhayMa10070532,India,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.776, 'pos': 0.224, 'compound': 0.6705}"
228,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,JustGill2020,,,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
229,Hasta cuándo el presidente   tomará con seriedad la pandemia del COVID 19 y actuará con responsabilid… ,ENMPCoahuila,Coahuila de Zaragoza,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
230," La propia OMS comparó al COVID-19 con la gripe española, que infectó a 1/3 de la población mundial. Esto… ",EstivenPi,,,"[('La propia OMS', 'FAC'), ('la gripe española', 'FAC'), ('que infectó', 'PERSON'), ('1/3', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
231,"   Un covid ? Lequel?..ni lui ni ses proches n""ont étés contaminés. Nous ne comptons pas..",RaymondBouillo1,"Marseille, France",,"[('ni lui ni', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
232,Coco wasn’t interested in feline covid news but wants to know where the volleyball went!   ,ampy1464,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.867, 'pos': 0.133, 'compound': 0.2828}"
233, Pota bilkul theek kita Main anti pti haan but covid da aaik he illaj vee Ainan nay nai kita karway… ,dentoon2002,"لاہور, پاکستان",,"[('Pota', 'ORG'), ('kita Main', 'ORG'), ('pti', 'ORG'), ('kita karway', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.08, 'neu': 0.92, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1655}"
234,Enhancing Customer Experience With Digital No Touch Payment In Covid-19 TimesRead :  ,winklix,"New York, USA",,"[('TimesRead', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.18, 'neu': 0.82, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
235,  ,Morne61573303,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
236,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,LifeBoatGeek,"Torpoint, England",,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
237, ,HopeFloatsVA,"Chuckatuck Creek, VA",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
238,"    Uh, Covid hasn’t been around for a decade.",nick_nuther,"Vegas, baby.",,"[('a decade', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
239,AfDB advances $27.4m to AU for COVID-19 response#BusinessAMLive #bbnaijalockdown2020,businessamlive,"Airport Road, Lagos, Nigeria",,"[('27.4', 'MONEY'), ('AU', 'ORG'), ('bbnaijalockdown2020', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
240, AAAAHHH REALLY??? I DESPISE IT ALSO SRY I HAVEN'T POSTED MUCH ART RECENTLY IM GOING THROUGH A STRESS… ,DiosShoes,Drawing Gwess,,[],"{'neg': 0.188, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4995}"
241,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,ctleamington,Leamington Spa,,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
242,"Usai Test Swab, 2 Pencari Suaka di Kalideres Positif Covid-19    #TauCepatTanpaBatas #BeritaTerkini #BeritaTerkini… ",okezonenews,Jakarta,,"[('Usai Test Swab', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
243,"COVID-19 के कुल मामले 14.83 लाख हुए, पिछले 24 घंटे में 47,703,राम मंदिर के लिए सज रही अयोध्या नगरी, पूरी दुनिया देखेगी भूमिपूजन",imaanand,Noida,,"[('14.83', 'CARDINAL'), ('24', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
244,They just opened this week! Alcoa City Schools announced someone has tested positive for COVID-19 at its middle sch… ,Darlene_Edw,United States,,"[('this week', 'DATE'), ('Alcoa City Schools', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.178, 'compound': 0.5983}"
245,   My understanding is that all COVID-19 cases in aged care facilities in Victoria… ,AlanBixter,Australia,,"[('Victoria', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.789, 'pos': 0.211, 'compound': 0.4939}"
246,"Sales at Greggs are still 25%+ down on this time in 2019, the baker has said.The chain registered a £62.2m loss f… ",telebusiness,London,,"[('Greggs', 'ORG'), ('25%+', 'CARDINAL'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('baker', 'PERSON'), ('62.2', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.103, 'neu': 0.897, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3182}"
247,Covid-19 accelerates South Africa's NHI plans ,BusinessTechSA,Gauteng,,"[('Covid-19 accelerates', 'ORG'), (""South Africa's"", 'GPE'), ('NHI', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
248, Por eso se va a Portugal.,ECastn,,,"[('Portugal', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
249,Mundo - Covid-19: Brasil regista 614 mortes e 23.284 casos em 24 horas ,revistaSABADO,"Lisboa, Portugal",,"[('614', 'CARDINAL'), ('23.284', 'CARDINAL'), ('24', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
250, #Bitcoin is indicator of World economy. Every-time economy shakes - BTC goes UP. BTC was created to… ,lostinhdr,,,"[('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('BTC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.882, 'pos': 0.118, 'compound': 0.25}"
251, No staff present at rainbow school to test covid 19 /refer ad in todays news papers.,Kuldeep57795482,"लखनऊ, भारत",,"[('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.128, 'neu': 0.872, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
252,,Jack65203,Columbia MO,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
253,one of my friends tested positive for COVID-19 today ahaiajhw,Monokosmos_96,,,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('today', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.544, 'pos': 0.456, 'compound': 0.7717}"
254, once covid clears up maybe I’ll have to see if the number one MIRA player in upstate NY can take the crown :p,EGOISM420,Equator Line 1st(they/them),,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('MIRA', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.8, 'pos': 0.2, 'compound': 0.4588}"
255, Masuk ICU covid lagi sedih ...,pinchorsalt,Malaysia,,"[('Masuk ICU', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
256,When men leave to go out; when children are away at school; the hour it takes to commute to work.. time alone in th… ,FaziliSana,,,"[('the hour', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.127, 'neu': 0.873, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
257, Stranger covid problem 😩,PavlikovskyJe,,,"[('Stranger', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.574, 'neu': 0.426, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4019}"
258,"  Nice try, but you seem to have overlooked a few things.Suicides are way up.Murders ha… ",HerrDeux,,,[],"{'neg': 0.076, 'neu': 0.797, 'pos': 0.126, 'compound': 0.1901}"
259, I have had one treatment in 5 months and feel like my cancer is coming back need scan to confirm wished I had… ,JacquelineColl7,Birmingham ,,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('5 months', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.177, 'neu': 0.723, 'pos': 0.1, 'compound': -0.4404}"
260,சென்னையில் கொரோனா நிலவரம் என்ன?#Chennai #COVID #COVID19 #coronavirus #CoronaUpdateswithJayaPlus ,jayapluschannel,Chennai,,"[('COVID', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
261,I may dislike cats but this shit sad as hell Cat becomes first animal to test positive for COVID-19 in the UK  ,thecoreymarks,Im a Disgrace blvd,,"[('Cat', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.466, 'neu': 0.409, 'pos': 0.125, 'compound': -0.9363}"
262,Militari con mitra e in assetto da guerra: le inutili (e umilianti) ronde anti-covid sulla spiaggia di Ventimigli..… ,Marco_Zum,Ovunque,,"[('Militari', 'GPE'), ('le inutili', 'PERSON'), ('Ventimigli', 'WORK_OF_ART')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
263,Klarifikasi atas beredarnya pemberitaan RS diuntungkan dari kasus Covid-19 ,VazaNadia,Indonesia,,"[('Klarifikasi atas beredarnya', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
264, Sounds like one of those Sinn Fein loopers.  They don't obey the Covid-19 rules anyway.,JakeBar66365454,,,"[('Sinn Fein', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.848, 'pos': 0.152, 'compound': 0.3612}"
265,"Ensuring women’s equal representation, participation and leadership in all COVID-19 response is essential to preven… ",fair_wl,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.2732}"
266,"I knew the switch from CDC to HHS Covid-19 reports could be problematic, but I didn't expect it to be this clear th… ",TheJWittz,"Seattle, WA",,"[('CDC', 'ORG'), ('HHS', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.078, 'neu': 0.762, 'pos': 0.16, 'compound': 0.4678}"
267, ,ChunkyFluffball,Republic of Croatia,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
268,"COVID-19 Claims Two More Lives, J&amp;K Toll Now 231 - ",KashmirLife,"Srinagar, Kashmir.",,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('231', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
269,"Every year flood happen in Bihar , why there is no precaution planning taken by Nitish Govt. The same way in Covid… ",bebak_awaz,,,"[('Every year', 'DATE'), ('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('Nitish Govt', 'PERSON'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.099, 'neu': 0.901, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
270," Massive financial mismanagement by Tories, meanwhile Annie Wells expresses ‘fury’ about an SNP logo o… ",indyscotnews,Europe,,"[('Tories', 'ORG'), ('Annie Wells', 'ORG'), ('SNP', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.875, 'pos': 0.125, 'compound': 0.25}"
271,"  If you are infected with covid while shopping at Wal-Mart, get a lawyer, get alot of lawyers.",Jennife60434825,,,"[('Wal-Mart', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.176, 'neu': 0.824, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4939}"
272,"As we battle against Covid-19, let us also be wary of Hepatitis – a disease that affects millions every year.… ",flamingohealth_,"Mumbai, India",,"[('Hepatitis', 'PERSON'), ('millions every year', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.133, 'neu': 0.867, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}"
273, I thank that is an covid symptom. Get checked,jesse06ray,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.737, 'pos': 0.263, 'compound': 0.3612}"
274,"I lost a friend today. They didn't die, they are  just a covid conspiracy theorist. Moreover a everything’s a cons… ",Pollypossible,"England, United Kingdom",,"[('today', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.247, 'neu': 0.477, 'pos': 0.275, 'compound': 0.1645}"
275,【2020年7月28日付更新】#インウェブアウト留学センター 更新：ハワイ州の #新型コロナウイルス （COVID-19）に関連する情報を随時更新し掲載、また、渡航に関する情報も同時に掲載しております。#ハワイ #コロナ… ,inwebout,日本 東京,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
276,Most Covid cases in Telangana in 31-40 years age group. ,sushilrTOI,"Hyderabad, India",,"[('Telangana', 'GPE'), ('31-40 years age', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
277,モロッコの地方自治体は、フェズでの症例数の増加に対応し、フェズでのショップ、カフェ、美容院の午後8時以降の営業を禁止しました。追って通知があるまで継続されます。#モロッコ… ,moroccohyakka,"Fez, Fès-Boulemane",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
278,"    When Trump finally gets COVID-19 (and he will), please treat hi… ",Leeny_Doll,,,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.643, 'pos': 0.357, 'compound': 0.6124}"
279,"Nearly 7 million more children could suffer from acute malnutrition due to Covid-19 pandemic,… ",OsendpNutrition,,,"[('Nearly 7\xa0million', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.239, 'neu': 0.761, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5809}"
280,swab covid teramatlat perit ye kakak kakak abang abang,pacehah,,,"[('swab', 'NORP'), ('perit ye kakak', 'PERSON'), ('abang abang', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
281,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,rachaelmck,"Salford, England",,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
282, explains why Covid-19 could become a mass-extinction event for small and medium-sized companies. Anywhere… ,splainerin,India,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
283,Antisipasi penyebaran covid 19 dan paham radikalisme #JagaNKRIdariHTIdanCovid ,sorot45,,,"[('Antisipasi penyebaran', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
284, Wale si walivuta ule mzigo wa Covid-19? sio kuwa wanatimiza masharti kweli,Giftedlawyer,"Dar es Salaam, Tanzania",,"[('Wale', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
285,"Mia mamma non vuole prestarmi il bagaglio a mano perché “vai in Francia, c’è il covid, meglio di no” 🥳🥳🥳🥳",september199six,april 4 2018 / Mystic Falls,,"[('Mia', 'ORG'), ('Francia', 'GPE'), ('c’è', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
286, To squeeze us and covid which is curricular,CorporateTO,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
287,"If you have symptoms, get a test today #COVID19 #NORTHAMPTONSHIRE #NorthantsTogether ",NTelegraph,Northamptonshire,,"[('today', 'DATE'), '', ('NorthantsTogether', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
288, लखनऊ विश्वविद्यालय द्वारा आयोजित होने वाली बीएड परीक्षा का सेंटर 200-300km दूर बनाया जा रहा है।।।ऐसे… ,PankajV88697334,"Allahabad, India",,"[('सेंटर 200-300km', 'MONEY'), ('बनाया', 'LAW')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
289,Disappointingly resetting the “Days since Bolsonaro contracts COVID” back from 7 to 0 at the Brazilian US Embassy ,h_e_n_r_y_s,"New York, NY",,"[('the “Days', 'DATE'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.162, 'neu': 0.838, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4404}"
290,Baleerrr xtau ke skng musim covid ni ... Nk politik pun berfikir ,qiejafry_,,,"[('Baleerrr xtau ke skng', 'PERSON'), ('Nk', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
291,"Quel dommage de ne pas avoir créer l'""Union Méditerranéenne""sous  : #opportunités #gestiondesrisques… ",laurence_bonnin,"Paris, France",,"[('l\'""Union', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
292, You really turned a corner during this Covid Volatility mate...showing a lot of other trader's just how its done,KellyFe48495867,"Gold Coast, Queensland",,"[('Covid Volatility', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
293, i don't get how they can even be doing this. This covid committee is not the Australian Govt. how do we end this farce?,nqwatcher,Australia,,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.876, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.481}"
294,I’m constantly flipping between anger and despair these days with regard to visiting my grandmother. It’s becoming… ,inconceivablykt,,,"[('these days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.295, 'neu': 0.705, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7414}"
295,"По словам председателя ФСМС, рассматриваются разные виды помощи — от поликлиники до реабилитационных центров и сана… ",villagekz,Kazakhstan,,"[('ФСМС', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
296,"If your parents are involved in the Covid heist, please tell them to channel the funds towards small black business at least.",Silindokuhle_,"Johannesburg, South Africa",,"[('Covid', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.901, 'pos': 0.099, 'compound': 0.3182}"
297,*Very Very Urgently Required A Positive Plasma Donors as the patient is on VENTILATOR*👉 Patient Name : VENKATESH👉… ,ShanmukaBhavani,"Hyderabad, India",,"[('VENTILATOR', 'ORG'), ('VENKATESH', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.795, 'pos': 0.205, 'compound': 0.5945}"
298,The ban on tobacco by the government has been disastrous. It has led to the illegal cigarette trade industry to mak… ,MadKay15,"Pretoria, South Africa",,[],"{'neg': 0.381, 'neu': 0.619, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9022}"
299,Pakistan urges worshippers to buy sacrificial animals online to prevent Covid-19 surge | Malay Mail ,malaymail,Malaysia,,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('| Malay Mail', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.805, 'pos': 0.195, 'compound': 0.2263}"
300,ಚೀನಾದಲ್ಲಿ ಸದ್ದಿಲ್ಲದೆ ಹೆಚ್ಚಾಗುತ್ತಿದೆ ಕೊರೋನಾ ಸೋಂಕಿತರ ಸಂಖ್ಯೆ..! ,MasthMagaa,,,"[('ಕೊರೋನಾ ಸೋಂಕಿತರ', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
301,Les  commentaires... représentatifs du bordel international. #covid ,French_bean,"Lille, France",,"[('représentatifs du bordel', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
302,  JackBREAKING: American Doctors Address COVID-19 Misinformation with SCOTUS Press Confere… ,Shawgirl72,"Washington, USA",,"[('American Doctors Address COVID-19 Misinformation', 'ORG'), ('SCOTUS Press Confere', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.204, 'neu': 0.796, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3182}"
303,Antisipasi penyebaran covid 19 dan paham radikalisme #JagaNKRIdariHTIdanCovid ,sorot45,,,"[('Antisipasi penyebaran', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
304,M'era venuto qualche dubbio che #Bocelli fosse scemo ... 'sto video me l'ha risolto definitivamente.👍Andrea Boce… ,Solegiallorosso,"Roma, Lazio",,"[(""M'era"", 'ORG'), ('Bocelli fosse', 'FAC'), ('Andrea Boce', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
305,سوق تقنيات التصوير الحيوي تحليل الأثر العالمي والإقليمي لـ Covid-19: تصوير براكو ، esaote و bayer – السياحة ,NewsAyn,,,"[('سوق تقنيات', 'PERSON'), ('الحيوي تحليل الأثر', 'PERSON'), ('تصوير براكو', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
306,Pandemic Expert: U.S. Schools Aren't Ready To Open Due To COVID-19 | The...  via … ,musicov197,,,"[('U.S.', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.15, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2755}"
307,"Three policemen, including a sub-inspector, suspended for alleged laxity in connection with kidnapping and murder o… ",JantaKaReporter,,,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8316}"
308," He’s trying to keep the covid out, but not the cocaine.",Saulville,"Los Angeles, CA",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
309,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,leanne8866,,,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
310, How does anyone believe we can come up with a safe vaccine when we can’t even come up with a safe and reli… ,BrokeCalifornia,"Homelessville, CA",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.766, 'pos': 0.234, 'compound': 0.7003}"
311,En  nos tomamos muy en serio tu salud y hemos fumigado contra el #COVID con  #TeCuidamos… ,VallAgenda,"Valladolid, Castilla y León",,"[('nos', 'ORG'), ('y hemos', 'PRODUCT'), ('COVID', 'ORG'), ('TeCuidamos', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
312,Traveling all over the place but scared to get covid. The logic... where is it?,AsSHaTtAcKk,Lost... always lost...,,[],"{'neg': 0.216, 'neu': 0.784, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5927}"
313," Hay tanta pendejada pasa curar el COVID-19MX!! No hay hará el día de hoy algo q ayude, nunca habrá cura nunc… ",cesarol27906392,,,"[('el día de hoy algo q ayude', 'PERSON'), ('nunca habrá cura', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.128, 'neu': 0.872, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4184}"
314,Northam urges Virginians to prepare for hurricane season amid COVID-19 pandemic ,NBC12,"Richmond, VA",,"[('Northam', 'ORG'), ('Virginians', 'NORP'), ('hurricane season', 'EVENT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
315,COVID has caused some of us lots of pain but the upgrading of our public healthcare infrastructure has been the sil… ,DanielMaithyaKE,"Nairobi, Kenya",,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.097, 'neu': 0.903, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2846}"
316,"  85% dei morti PER il Covid-19, 15% CON il Covid-19 (dati dell'ISS). Ammesso che questa distinzione abbia un senso",MarabottiMarco,"Toscana, Italia",,"[('85%', 'PERCENT'), ('15%', 'PERCENT'), ('il', 'GPE'), (""dell'ISS"", 'DATE'), ('Ammesso', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
317,Pemkab Wonogiri Siapkan Tiga Tempat Isolasi untuk Nakes Positif Covid-19 - #INDONESIA,IDCorner,"Central Java, Indonesia",,"[('Tiga Tempat Isolasi', 'PERSON'), ('Nakes Positif', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
318,Cuando participamos en la Comisión por el Futuro de Zaragoza 🤝 pedimos ayudas al comercio de proximidad y las peque… ,ActoraConsumo,"Zaragoza, España",,"[('de proximidad y las peque', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
319,Intel-powered supercomputers advancing #COVID19 research at scales from global to microscopic #HPC #IAmIntel ,IoTogether,"München, Bayern",,"[('Intel', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
320,"Los dispositivos personales nos ayudan mucho, pero nos 'venden' mucho también. (New York Times Report… ",RafaelPalominoP,"Alicante, España",,"[('Los dispositivos', 'GPE'), ('nos ayudan mucho', 'PERSON'), (""pero nos '"", 'PERSON'), ('mucho también', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('New York Times Report', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
321,"Right deployment model, strong partnerships, and the balance between technology and human empathy - these are the c… ",TP_Greece,Greece,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.171, 'compound': 0.5106}"
322,"Column from today on Temple &amp; Webster’s numbers today. Clearly a question mark on its current valuation, but zoom w… ",MrJThomson,Melbourne,,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('Temple &amp', 'ORG'), ('Webster', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.907, 'pos': 0.093, 'compound': 0.2144}"
323,In case you missed it in early July. Written by  : Scenarios for the Covid-19 and Post-Covid-19 Worlds – a… ,kdel1473,"Canberra, Australia",,"[('early July', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.115, 'neu': 0.885, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
324,Another 70 billion loan to the country 😔COVID will never end in sa,VallyM,"Johannesburg, South Africa",,"[('70 billion', 'CARDINAL'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
325,Lady Zamar slams the government officials for stealing COVID-19 funds ,news365coza,Johannesburg,,"[('Lady Zamar', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.291, 'neu': 0.709, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5719}"
326,Did you know? The premiere of #Aliens was 34 years ago. And  is still reminding us to stay safe!… ,APFInnovation,,,"[('Aliens', 'PERSON'), ('34 years ago', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
327,"  Yo veo 2 “bandos”1- El gobierno. Todo mal, no hay nada que decir bien de estos. 2- La… ",Falque,,,"[('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('El', 'ORG'), ('Todo mal', 'PERSON'), ('nada que decir bien de estos', 'FAC'), ('La', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.121, 'neu': 0.879, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
328,     Covid loves for-profit aged care.,AussieCitizen1,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.303, 'pos': 0.697, 'compound': 0.7845}"
329,8      Are you letting people know that you're alive on #socialmedia during the  #COVID-19 #pandemic? Read my… ,conpsweeney,NYC Area,,"[('8', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.852, 'pos': 0.148, 'compound': 0.3818}"
330,Flood of COVID-19-related lawsuits expected to hit courts | CBC News  If you have just half… ,stardaz11,"Ontario, Canada",,"[('COVID-19-related', 'ORG'), ('CBC News', 'ORG'), ('just half', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.103, 'neu': 0.897, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1531}"
331,На Украине за сутки выявили 919 случаев COVID-19 ,plusnovosti,Москва,,"[('На Украине', 'PERSON'), ('919', 'CARDINAL'), ('случаев', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
332,Nearly 3 out of 4 business leaders see cybersecurity as a top priority in COVID-19 recovery  ,IDCPSavings,"Orange, CA",,"[('Nearly 3', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': 0.2023}"
333,Perkembangan uji klinis vaksin COVID-19 di Indonesia.#ElshintaEdisiSiang,elshinta_smg,"Jawa Tengah, Indonesia",,"[('Perkembangan', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
334,World's biggest COVID-19 Vaccine study begins in US; Biocon drug rejected ,ForbesIndia,Mumbai,,"[('World', 'ORG'), ('Vaccine', 'PRODUCT'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Biocon', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5106}"
335,#declareSBIJApreResult2020Pls declare the result of sbi clerk 2020.Its been nearly 5 monthsPressure is enhancing.… ,DhepeJalindar,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
336,Antisipasi penyebaran covid 19 dan paham radikalisme #JagaNKRIdariHTIdanCovid ,sorot45,,,"[('Antisipasi penyebaran', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
337,Just imagine how Ghana 🇬🇭 would have been without the  -  talks about management of COVID-… ,Jake_Fianu,"Accra, Ghana..",,"[('Ghana 🇬🇭', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
338,"ATUALIZAÇÃO COVID-198 HorasCasos - 2.449.418Óbitos - 87.840Recuperados - 1.848.376 (75,46%)Ativos - 513.202 (… ",g1coronavirus,Brasil,,"[('HorasCasos', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
339,"U.S. accuses Chinese nationals of hacking spree targeting COVID data, defense secrets | Reuters ",CyberSecInt,Oxford,,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.161, 'neu': 0.738, 'pos': 0.101, 'compound': -0.2263}"
340,"En Amérique du Nord, Google vient de prolonger le télétravail au moins jusqu'en juillet 2021. La direction du géant… ",zdnetfr,Paris,,"[('Amérique du Nord', 'PERSON'), ('Google', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
341,"7 months on from our #Sustainable Business Advent Calendar a lot has changed in the world of #business, with challe… ",NOA_Ltd,"Oxford, UK",,"[('7 months', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
342,#CLAVES | Los jugadores de béisbol no escapan de la pandemia de #COVID19. Hasta el pasado #2jul se habían reportado… ,ElPitazoTV,Venezuela,,"[('CLAVES', 'PERSON'), ('Hasta el pasado #2jul', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
343,"Poi il cantante precisa: ""Accadono cose strane. Sono stato frainteso"" ",repubblica,"Rome, Italy",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
344,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,GillyDore,United Kingdom,,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
345,The Disability Royal Commission is set to resume public hearings this week. Listen to this podcast to find out wh… ,SummerFoundtn,Australia,,"[('The Disability Royal Commission', 'ORG'), ('this week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
346, Many of those that have mild Covid-19 infections may get cardiac damage (heart involvement).Will that af… ,DrAmarMOH,Malaysia,,[],"{'neg': 0.176, 'neu': 0.824, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4939}"
347,#HelphenIndia #lockdown #COVID #mumbai #storiesuntold #autowala #stayhome #staysafe #CommonMan #helphen… ,HelphenIndia,"Tamil Nadu, India",,"[('HelphenIndia', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
348,Dosing commences in Phase III trial of Moderna’s Covid-19 vaccine  ,ArenaClinical,"London, England",,"[('Moderna', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
349,３　クロロキンを押しまくって製薬業界を恐怖の底に陥れているトランプに製薬会社と争う勇気がないという見方は間違っている。ワクチンの害も熟知。ならなぜCovid-19のワクチンを絶大プッシュするのか？大統領就任からワクチン批判は封印しCovid以来ワクチン推進派。,YattsukeBlog,Trust the plan. Q,,"[('３', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
350,And the cure for covid is....,stormgalNYC,NYC,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
351,COVID 19 following us into 2021 ,SupremeSulay,The field,,"[('COVID', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
352,I’ve struggled to read non-fiction since Covid-19. And Sway is a very academic research book. So I’ve found it very… ,duffyeva,Never far away from a book.,,"[('Sway', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.118, 'neu': 0.882, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.34}"
353,"*NO* supermarket should do this. These people are selfish, stubborn twats, with no compassion for those who might d… ",pilgrim4j1,,,[],"{'neg': 0.308, 'neu': 0.577, 'pos': 0.115, 'compound': -0.6124}"
354,  Aí eu teria de perguntar o q minha mulher acha (manja demais de corticoides devido às esp… ,fabiomoraes,,,"[('manja', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
355,…/onslaught-interview-with-nige-rock…Onslaught Interview with Nig… ,gods_meltdown,"North East, England",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
356,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,ActivityHol,London,,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
357,"    Sir,many thanks for your prompt action.Kindly allow educational e… ",manoranjan1090,"Bhubaneshwar, Orissa",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.593, 'pos': 0.407, 'compound': 0.5859}"
358,"  ""They"" have been spreading the word across the media how your own antibodies ""don't guaran… ",212TruthSeeker,"New York, NY",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
359,  What was he promised? Some sweet biden admin position for keeping Wa under his boot.Why… ,DCThelma,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.703, 'pos': 0.297, 'compound': 0.6705}"
360,       … ,AK56A1,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
361,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,SamWardman,"West Cornwall, UK",,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
362,"While we are reeling under the effects of the covid-19 pandemic, let’s not forget about viral #hepatitis which can… ",hthealthshots,"New Delhi, India",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.915, 'pos': 0.085, 'compound': 0.1695}"
363,"UP: Ambulance driver wearing PPE kit faints while ferrying COVID-19 patients, fifth incident in 15 days.",TimesNow,India,,"[('Ambulance', 'ORG'), ('PPE', 'ORG'), ('fifth', 'ORDINAL'), ('15 days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
364,My memories are making me sad af ! I’m always on a vacation around this time 🥺 pinche COVID wey,paola_zuazua,"corpus christi, tx",,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.175, 'neu': 0.825, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5255}"
365,"No question the Covid-19 pandemic can place a hardship on couples, making dating nearly impossible and putting a st… ",abc7breaking,El Paso,,[],"{'neg': 0.231, 'neu': 0.769, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5423}"
366,"Seven months into the pandemic, COVID-19 is still having an impact on the police and fire departments, from their b… ",KMVTNews,"Twin Falls, ID",,"[('Seven months', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.112, 'neu': 0.888, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.34}"
367,"  There have been many drugs that inhibit viruses in vitro, which fail to be effective i… ",inquiringnative,United States,,[],"{'neg': 0.275, 'neu': 0.586, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': -0.4588}"
368,I can’t believe I know actual people who truly believe that Covid will just go away after the election. It boggles… ,AlexLeeDrums,"Phoenix, Arizona",,"[('Covid', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.861, 'pos': 0.139, 'compound': 0.4404}"
369,Though I know it wasn’t COVID bc I’m pretty sure bleeding out ur ear wasn’t a symptom lol,loneIywatson,Genderfluid -20 yrs- Lesbian,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.61, 'pos': 0.39, 'compound': 0.8074}"
370,"   Bro, hindi tumitigil ang mundo dahil lang sa covid. Maraming dapat asikasu… ",OmarMars10,,,"[('hindi tumitigil ang mundo dahil lang sa covid', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
371,"Kya aise he bartav kiya jata hai Covid patient ke sath,Lanat hai aisi vwavasth par… ",devubetu77,"Kanpur, India",,"[('Kya', 'PERSON'), ('ke sath', 'PERSON'), ('Lanat hai', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
372,"If true..truely Sad.. But we would like to see the blood results, tests results, and Coroners report.",TexasCru2020,"Dallas, Texas.",,"[('Coroners', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.865, 'pos': 0.135, 'compound': 0.3612}"
373,"Mai aur mera chota bhai kal Covid-19 positive aya hu, maine ghar par isolate hone ka vikalp chuna hai, kal dr ki te… ",devubetu77,"Kanpur, India",,"[('bhai kal', 'PERSON'), ('aya hu', 'PERSON'), ('maine', 'GPE'), ('hone ka vikalp chuna hai', 'PERSON'), ('kal dr ki te', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.068, 'neu': 0.795, 'pos': 0.136, 'compound': 0.4215}"
374," ...è estate, c’è il sole... machissenefrega del covid... è tempo di #cicale",bash_qwerty,,,"[('machissenefrega del covid', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
375,   The hospital gets more money for COVID. ,JoeScarab,,,"[('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
376, There was more than 2 but those 2 counted for most deaths and again private aged care see the similarities… ,Laughatsaltyge1,,,"[('more than 2', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.798, 'pos': 0.202, 'compound': 0.6486}"
377,"Pues resulta que tengo anticuerpos del covid, asi que ya he pasado al bicho. Menuda máquina.",Sincerebroninah,Madrid.        ,,"[('asi que', 'PERSON'), ('al bicho', 'PERSON'), ('Menuda máquina', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
378,"Kova, stam1nan Viimeinen Atlantis - konsertti siirtyi joulua edeltävälle sunnuntaille. Samana lauantaina ois Raskas… ",feuer__,Tampere,,"[('Kova', 'PERSON'), ('Viimeinen Atlantis -', 'PERSON'), ('joulua edeltävälle sunnuntaille', 'PERSON'), ('Samana', 'GPE'), ('Raskas', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
379,India in better position in fighting COVID 19 says Modi😒😒oh !!! Really??,NishaShekh,Earth,,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('COVID', 'ORG'), ('Modi😒', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.15, 'neu': 0.601, 'pos': 0.249, 'compound': 0.3891}"
380,"Attorney’s Offices for the Northern, Southern, Western, and Eastern Districts of Texas, today informed the public a… ",TBBusiness,"McAllen, Texas",,"[('Southern', 'NORP'), ('Western', 'LOC'), ('Eastern', 'ORG'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
381,Antisipasi penyebaran covid 19 dan paham radikalisme #JagaNKRIdariHTIdanCovid ,sorot45,,,"[('Antisipasi penyebaran', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
382,Could be my favorite Covid tweet ever. ,marksfamof8,Oregon,,"[('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.667, 'pos': 0.333, 'compound': 0.4588}"
383,"  Considering the effects that Covid-19 ""long-termers"" are reporting, I'll take my chan… ",Fen_Ra,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
384,It's going to be hard going back to wearing bras once this covid thing is over lol,lady_zemmy,"California, USA",,[],"{'neg': 0.073, 'neu': 0.781, 'pos': 0.146, 'compound': 0.34}"
385, : Please initiate refund for below PNR. The PNR were impacted due to Covid1)PNR: XEW4XL (Booking date :… ,GPohuja,,,"[('PNR', 'ORG'), ('PNR', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.126, 'compound': 0.3182}"
386, You're a wonderful friend and person! I like you and sorry for being so distant but COVID-19 has been a shit 😩💖,literallyanimu1,,,[],"{'neg': 0.228, 'neu': 0.527, 'pos': 0.245, 'compound': -0.2828}"
387,"Pour ceux, politiciens, représentants de groupes professionnels et même experts scientifiques, qui avec l'aplomb qu… ",jpmarthoz,Belgium,,"[('qui', 'ORG'), (""l'aplomb qu"", 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
388,静岡県内本日の新規感染者数は11名これで静岡県内新型コロナウイルス感染者数は210名となった2020/07/28 15:54現在#新型コロナ #静岡コロナ,Shizuoka_COVID,静岡県,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
389,Tricks governors used to ‘meet’ 300-bed order ,MacOtani,"Nairobi, KENYA",,[],"{'neg': 0.2, 'neu': 0.8, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.128}"
390,  The problem is you are still trying to contain a virus that cannot be contained.  g… ,abirballan,,,[],"{'neg': 0.162, 'neu': 0.838, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4019}"
391, That’s me most nights LOL when I still had a job pre covid I worked nights so that’s my schedule 😂,kksloane,Zoeopolis,,"[('most nights', 'TIME'), ('LOL', 'PERSON'), ('nights', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.808, 'pos': 0.192, 'compound': 0.5874}"
392," Good morning Ashwani, Yes, however there are a few things you must consider before travelling to Heath… ",HeathrowAirport,"London, England",,"[('Ashwani', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.714, 'pos': 0.286, 'compound': 0.6808}"
393, Vcs nunca pensam no bem geral da população. Só pensam nos interesses de vcs. E se houvesse a greve… ,ronaldofiore,Brasil,,"[('nos', 'ORG'), ('de vcs', 'PERSON'), ('houvesse', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.121, 'neu': 0.879, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
394, I don’t understand the logic of how private schools can provide lessons and the state schools can’t?… ,NickyBr19027366,"Cobham, South East",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
395,     I’ve got this ,Pugfrench2,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
396,"      No, dear. You’ve got it backwards. COVI… ",politixalt,,,[],"{'neg': 0.224, 'neu': 0.51, 'pos': 0.265, 'compound': 0.1027}"
397,     Correct. Yet press keep referring to it as the… ,Jim_Pembroke,Brisbane,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
398, Why didn’t we move covid patients to the empty hospital they put up specially for covid so that cancer patient… ,izy5remi13,,,[],"{'neg': 0.265, 'neu': 0.735, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7564}"
399,Antisipasi penyebaran covid 19 dan paham radikalisme #JagaNKRIdariHTIdanCovid ,sorot45,,,"[('Antisipasi penyebaran', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
400,        Umm...… ,flitesurgn,USA,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
401,"Alm me doy un chingo de risa, maldita calentura!!! Ya vete covid 😭😭",KatiaryG,,,"[('de risa', 'PERSON'), ('maldita calentura', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
402,"Worth a read, but wish in addition to #inequality ⁦ had also looked at how to finance global public go… ",KatriBertram,"Berlin, Germany",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.762, 'pos': 0.238, 'compound': 0.6124}"
403,The Secretary of State for Health Matt Hancock: Stop unnecessary cancer deaths caused by the COVID disruptions and… ,dsue1441_re,,,"[('State', 'ORG'), ('Matt Hancock', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.375, 'neu': 0.625, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8402}"
404,Coronavirus: BAME groups disproportionately fined for COVID-19 breaches  ,sblissett999me1,,,"[('BAME', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
405,  Do you know why?No mail left into New Zealand.If We lived on an Island maybe we could s… ,PatMoloney8,"Cork, Ireland",,"[('why?No', 'PRODUCT'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
406,Allonlineoutlet | Here’s Exactly Where We Are with Vaccines and Treatments for COVID-19… ,Nandsoft8,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
407,"   She has seen 350 out of the over 15,000 Covid cases in Houston. No clarificati… ",RossRhod,,,"[('350', 'CARDINAL'), ('15,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('Houston', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.136, 'neu': 0.864, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
408,How a global crisis turns into a personal crisis  via ,gpalchemia,"Baden-Württemberg, Deutschland",,[],"{'neg': 0.577, 'neu': 0.423, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8481}"
409,    哟？这扣帽子的功夫学挺快啊，这不是你先歧视我们的吗？怎么这语气好像是我在说你使得。我印象中，香蕉人的意思难道不是美国… ,LittleBoy5cm,深圳~,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
410, ... Può essere che il covid gli ha bruciato il cervello?,ErnestoSparal19,"San Donato Milanese, Lombardia",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.806, 'pos': 0.194, 'compound': 0.34}"
411,  Yes but twitter took down site of Doctors telling the truth about Covid.,karenwo33128259,,,"[('Covid', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.696, 'pos': 0.304, 'compound': 0.5859}"
412, 2005 NIH said chloroquine kills SARS-COVID.,RichardCkark,"Athens, AL",,"[('2005', 'DATE'), ('NIH', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.412, 'neu': 0.588, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5423}"
413,"‼️В Украине — 66 575 человек болеют COVID-19Из них 1629 пациентов умерли, 36 744 — выздоровели. За сутки +919 новы… ",nakipeloua,Харків,,"[('Украине', 'GPE'), ('66 575 человек', 'QUANTITY'), ('36 744', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
414," plan for municipal PipMoyer Rec Ctr equally unsafe, masks not required while exercising indoors. M… ",jnannapolis,Annapolis,,"[('PipMoyer Rec Ctr', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
415,Todo vale con la excusa de la COVID 19 y encima hemos de callar 🤫 por miedo.   … ,PilarParreno,"Valencia, Comunidad Valenciana",,"[('19 y encima', 'QUANTITY'), ('\U0001f92b', 'FAC')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
416,"•UK Eyes France, Germany After Slapping COVID-19 Quarantine On Spain*FG, Resident Doctors Begin Negotiation To Ave… ",olapeckham,"Ikeja, Nigeria",,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Quarantine', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
417,"       Sir Chandra babu garu, why don't you come to… ",sontipartha,,,"[('Chandra', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
418,Kopat-kopit...Ujung2e denda ya glemeke pol2an...Cempuleke covid-19 mung ....Penguasa Sukses Bisnis Basah..Razia… ,GLAGAH_PANUNTUN,,,"[('Kopat-kopit', 'PERSON'), ('Ujung2e denda ya glemeke', 'PERSON'), ('Cempuleke', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
419, Lah remed covid awoakwow,iniakunnyaaku_,,,"[('Lah', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
420, and  congratulations to both of you !!! In the time of covid crisis and the biggest pend… ,Maheshd08308689,"Hyderabad, India",,[],"{'neg': 0.208, 'neu': 0.628, 'pos': 0.163, 'compound': -0.2677}"
421," Non serve un giudice, Fontana dopo la grande confusione nella gestione del Covid, la regione con più… ",vitosemeraro7,"Puglia, Italia",,"[('Fontana', 'ORG'), ('la grande', 'PERSON'), ('nella gestione del Covid', 'FAC'), ('la regione', 'FAC')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
422, Kok bisa ditilang sih? Kan lagi covid mah gaada razia motor,SyahrulAM13,Dimana-mana hatiku senang,,"[('Kok', 'PERSON'), ('ditilang sih', 'PERSON'), ('Kan lagi', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
423,   ,david4potus2020,"Murfreesboro, Tennessee",,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
424,"Animal Genetics Market Worth $5.8 billion | Impact of Covid 19, Segmentation &amp; Major Key Players -… ",eprnetwork,US,,"[('$5.8 billion', 'MONEY'), ('Segmentation &amp', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.888, 'pos': 0.112, 'compound': 0.2263}"
425,The scientists 3D printing skin and miniature organs:,robinhowie,London,,"[('3D', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
426,  ,stevesms1960,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
427,"In his message, #UN chief #AntonioGuterres said urban areas were ground zero of the #COVID19pandemic, with 90 per c… ",FinancialXpress,"New Delhi, India",,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('AntonioGuterres', 'ORG'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('90', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
428,,teresagranda1,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
429,     And then went to a strip club to get  foo… ,yeeitsearl,,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
430,As 🇰🇪 President H.E Uhuru Kenyatta was preparing to impose a 30 day ban on the sake of alcohol (due to Covid linked… ,KatendeSoogi,"Kampala, Uganda",,"[('H.E Uhuru Kenyatta', 'ORG'), ('30 day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.225, 'neu': 0.775, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7003}"
431,Food by Abounding Grace Foundation will eradicate hunger in Nigeria during this Covid-19 season.Evangelist Christi… ,Prisonervoice2,London,,"[('Abounding Grace Foundation', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('this Covid-19 season', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.112, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.157, 'compound': 0.2023}"
432,"El ‘ultra prime’, ante el Covid-19: menos operaciones, pero más caras  via ",terralpainvest1,Madrid,,"[('El', 'ORG'), ('ante el', 'PERSON'), ('pero más', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
433,"""We have completed 2,000 #VandeBharat evacuations, bringing home 6.7 lakh Indians and flying out countless others.… ",MahtabNama,"Dehli, from #Supaul, Bihar",,"[('2,000 #VandeBharat', 'MONEY'), ('6.7', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indians', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
434,"""On les a condamnés avant même qu'ils ne soient contaminés"" : ces résidents d'Ehpad qui ont été privés d'hôpital au… ",SantonsSolognot,clery st andre (orleans),,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
435,"COVID-19 UPDATE: 25 na bagong kaso ng COVID-19 naitala ngayong araw sa Las Piñas, 5 naman nadagdag sa mga gumaling,… ",DonBuenvenida,💕 Nissin Riño Aceres 💕0530,,"[('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('5 naman', 'QUANTITY'), ('sa mga gumaling', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
